everydaysale.co.uk 2012-06-11

# everydaySALE - Privacy Policy

EverydaySale is dedicated to respect and guard your privacy.

This privacy policy is based on the principles that any private data you offer to us, or we gather from you, will be preserved seriously by us. Please see the followings in detail to know our points and processes refer to your private data.

To surf on our site, first of all, you should finish your registration form. You will be asked to submit your contact data, like name and email address, during registration. We will use this data to inform you the services that you have expressed an interest in. It is optional for you to fill in your other demographic information, including what are referring to your social networks which will enable us to acquire the data available in public, but in order to offer you a more personalised experience, we encourage you to do so.

## Data We Might Gather from You

We may gather and handle the following data about you:

  * Data you offer by filling in the forms on our website everydaysale.co.uk. These data includes what you provided during your registering for our posting discounts, newsletter and other material made by us. We will also require you for information as you report a website problem.
  * We may store a record of your correspondence sent to us.
  * We might also require you to finish some surveys we use for analysis purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

## Direct Mailings

When you register on everydaysale.co.uk or sign up for any of our information or newsletters, we will send you our discount codes’ information, 'free stuff', or other services and information we think can interest you.

By offering your email address, you agree to receive our proper newsletter emails from everydaysale.co.uk. You can subscribe our newsletter via submitting their email address at any of the subscribing boxes featured throughout the site or through the User Registration page.

We promise to use your personal information only in accordance with the legal requirements, principles and best practice recommendations of the Data Protection Act, which guaranty your various rights in respect of the handling of your personal information.

## Where We Keep Your Personal Information

The information which we gather from you may be transferred to, and kept at a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, processing or storing. We will make each step reasonably necessary to guarantee that your information is treated safely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

We keep all information you offered in our secure servers. Where you have chosen (or we have given you) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible to keep this password confidential. You are required not to share a password with anyone. 

But unfortunately, it is not fully safe to transmit data by internet. Though we will do our best to preserve your private data, we cannot ensure the security of your data transferred to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have got your information, we will use them in strict steps and security features to try to prevent any unauthorised access.

## Uses of the Information

We will only use data held about you in the following ways:

  * To guarantee what content from our site is presented in the most effective method for you and your computer.
  * To offer you with products, information or services that you ask from us or which we feel can interest you, where you have agreed to subscribe for such purposes.
  * To fulfill our obligations arising from any subscription entered into between you and us. 
  * When you choose to do so, to admit you to take part in interactive features of our service.
  * To inform you for any changes of our service.

We may also apply your information to offer you the data about products and services which may interest you.

We never reveal data about identifiable individuals to our affiliate advertisers, but we may offer them with aggregate data about our users.

## About Disclosure of Your Data

It’s your right to require us not to handle your private information for commercial aims. If we are ready to use your data for such aims, before to gather your information, we will normally tell you. Sometimes, our site may have mutual linkages with the websites of third parties. If you go after such a linkage to any one of these websites, please see through their own privacy policies for that we can’t take any liability and duty for their policies. We recommend you to read these policies in detail prior to your submitting any personal information to these websites.

We are sure to post it on this page if there is any change in our site’s privacy policy for information protection in the future.

Welcome to email us any comments, requests and questions refer to our information protection and privacy policy at [everydaysale_uk@hotmail.com](mailto:everydaysale_uk@hotmail.com)
